# Norbert Majer



I am a former deputy team leader and paramedic now undertaking a career change as a Tech Trainee.

After a successful healthcare career, I now want to express my creativity through technology. I love the diversity of challenges in this sector and the possibility of solving problems in multiple ways.

I like how technologies are changing and improving our lives, and I am impassioned to contribute to this development with my innovative thinking, creativity and skills.

Apart from work, I play table tennis, I swim, and I love to cook. Also, I like discovering new places, meeting new people, and trying exotic food.

### **SUMMARY**

I attained a Bachelor's degree in Paramedic science, and I am currently a Tech Trainee at future proof.

I loved my previous roles, but my interest in technology has been expanding in the recent year, and I began studying programming. I have created a <u>portfolio</u> <u>website</u> and built a few websites and apps.

The turning point occurred a year ago when I decided to change my career to technology. Since then, I have been purposefully learning tech skills. As a senior healthcare professional, I mastered several transferable skills during my healthcare career, such as problem-solving, teamwork, attention to detail, resilience, patience, and working under pressure.

I am now looking forward to pursuing a new career in the tech industry and handling new challenges.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

#### futureproof | Tech Trainee | July 2022 - September 2022

- 13-week bootcamp covering the main areas of web development, including JavaScript, HTML/CSS, Databases, and Python.
- Recently completed a 1-week group project using React to create a trivia quiz, using Jest and Enzyme to test.

#### Paramedic | [April 2009 - July 2022]

- Worked in different countries in several busy healthcare settings.
- Successfully communicated and liaised with team members, patients and relatives in emergencies.

#### Deputy Team Leader / Instructor | [September 2010 - August 2015]

- Conducted medical training with presentations and workshops
- Managed and led a team of twenty people
- Communicated medical centre goals and deadlines to the team
- Motivated team members and assessed performance
- Managed and edited the monthly schedule of the team

#### **EDUCATION**

# University of Hertfordshire | January 2020 – June 2020 | Postgraduate individual modules:

- Advanced health assessment and diagnostic indicators (level 7)
- Minor illness diagnostics and interventions (level 7)

#### University of Debrecen | 2002 - 2008] |

- Paramedic Science BSc (Hons)

# **FIND OUT MORE**

Gitl-

GitHub profile

in

LinkedIn

Portfolio website

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

HTML/CSS

JavaScript / Node.js

Git/GitHub

React.js

Python

Bootstrap